{
    "id": "687c56ac0b7d45eaabefd26852b348f3",
    "title": "Articles With Uncountable Nouns",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We need a secretary with ……………………. knowledge of Spanish.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "a good",
                "the good"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She speaks ……………………. English.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "a good",
                "the good"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you got …………………… for dry hair?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shampoo",
                "a shampoo",
                "the shampoo"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She has been such ……………………… help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "great",
                "a great",
                "the great"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "All that you need is …………………… sleep.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "a good",
                "the good"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We are having …………………. weather.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "terrible",
                "a terrible",
                "the terrible"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has made …………………… progress.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "a good",
                "the good"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My parents gave me ………………… education.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "a good",
                "the good"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She doesn’t have ……………………… understanding of the subject.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "a good",
                "the good"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I love listening to ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wind",
                "a wind",
                "the wind"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}